AUNG KO KO MIN

Web Developer

No.82 (b), Marlarmying 5th street, 16 ward, Hlaing Township, Yangon.

+959 421036937, +959 791848415

aungkokomin.official@gmail.com

LinkedIn - https://www.linkedin.com/in/aungkokomin/



PERSONAL SUMMARY

Efficient Junior Web Developer with a B.Sc.(Hon) Degree in IT and 3 years of experience in challenging development environments. Excellent communication and organizational abilities with resourceful approach to solving diverse problems. Deadline-driven and knowledgeable professional with strong desire to learn and contribute to team success. Collaborative and hardworking team player with critical thinking skill and systematic approach.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Junior Web Developer

GroovezAsia (Sept 2015 – Aug 2016)

- Developed CV Collecting and Management System for a Job Seeker Agent
- Handled hosting data for Miss Golden Land Website

Junior Web Developer

Apex Group Company (Sept 2016 – July 2018)

- Developed an in-house web app using PHP(Laravel), HTML/CSS, Javascript that allowed the users to calculate the Gas & Oil terminal related data
- Developed a Point-of-Sale system for Gas & Oil Company which is included the credit system to determine the Petro prices according to customer level.
- Worked across the software development life cycle to gather user requirements and build and maintain the code for the tools which can show the Oil Terminal data for different customers
- Coordinate with IT Manager to provide the required data and involved at providing trainings for the clients
- Developed a small content management system based on Laravel to build several company profile pages
- Experienced at using: PHP, Laravel, Git, HTML, CSS, Jquery, JSON, MySql, Ubuntu (Linux), Digital Ocean (Hosting) and Godaddy (Hosting)

SKILLS AND COMPETENCIES

- Web Dev Skills: HTML, CSS, PHP, JavaScript, Laravel
- Familiar with using Linux OS especially Ubuntu
- Have fair knowledge of domains & hosting
- Have good understanding about business structures
- Can grasp new tech or concept easily.
- Have good communication skill.
- Can lead a team.
- Built a POS system in College Project and an Online Learning Platform as University Project.
- Microsoft Office (Words, Excel, PowerPoint etc.)

VOLUNTEERING EXPERIENCE

As a normal volunteer in Student Council of KMD (June 2013 – December 2013)

As a Secretary in Student Council of KMD (January 2014 – June 2014)

As a President in Student Council of KMD (June 2014 – December 2014)

As a volunteer in some donation organizations' activities

EDUCATION

Third Year (Math)

Dagon University of Distance Education (2013 – 2014)

Second Year AGTI

West Yangon Technology University (2009 – 2011)

• High School Graduation Certificate

Practicing High School Yangon Institute of Education (TTC) (2008)

PROFESSIONAL QUALIFICATIONS

DEGREES AND DIPLOMAS

• Level 5 Diploma in Computing

NCC Education (2016)

• BSc (Hons) Business Information Technology

University of Greenwich (2018)

CERTIFICATES

• Certificate of Completion Post-Intermediate Level in English

Wall Street English (2019)

Advanced Web Developing Course

Fairway Dev (2015)

• Basic Programming (Java & PHP)

KMD Computer Training Center (2013)

Microsoft Office (2010)

KMD Computer Training Center (2013)

PERSONAL PARTICULAR

Age – 28

Gender – Male

Language Proficiency - Burmese (Mother Tongue), English (Intermediate)

Interests – Traditional Sports (Football, Tennis etc.), Esport, Reading